Eugene Otto Weber Murman Watercolors of California Flora, 1941-1961
Louise M. Darling Biomedical Library History and Special Collections Division
- Viscaceae [Loranthaceae] (Christmas Mistletoe) Family. 1958, Series 88.; 3 entries
  - Arceuthobium campylopodum (pine mistletoe). (Box 11, Folder 204)
    no collection date; throughout California foothills and mountains, chiefly on pine species, occationally on Abies. congolor (fr. Jepson); plate indicates Family: Loranthaceae
  - Phoradendron californicum (California mistletoe).4/12/58, photograph by Arvid L. Murman (Box 19, Folder 365)
    Morongo Valley, San Bernardino County; found on Larrea; plate indicates Family: Loranthaceae
  - Phoradendron californicum (California mistletoe).5/17/58 (Box 19, Folder 366)
    Morongo Valley, San Bernardino County; plate indicates Family: Loranthaceae
- Zygophyllaceae (Creosote-bush [Caltrops]) Family. 1954, Series 89.; 1 entry
  - Larrea divaricata (creosote bush; hediondilla).2/20/54 (Box 16, Folder 312)
    Death Valley, Inyo County